<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MindYourWay</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Enter Address, City or Zip Code</string>
    <string name="coordinates">Enter coordinates</string>
    <string name="start_journey">"Start Your Journey"</string>
    <string name="enter_nickname">Enter Nickname</string>
    <string name="credits">"Credits"</string>
    <string name="guide">"Guide"</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Mind Your Way is a game where you visit checkpoints around the map.\nFrom the main city view different region can be seen, separated by outlines. Tap on a region to select it. At the start only the Center region is unlocked, but as you progress you will unlock more!The level range of each region signifies its difficulty\nOnce you press \"Go to this region\", you will see the checkpoints represented by differently colored circles: [img src=btncirclew/], [img src=btncirclex/]. Select one that is available, but not reached yet, and press \"Go to location\". This will open a Google Maps screen where you can view your position [img src=ic_gps/] and  your destination [img src=ic_dest/]. When you reach your destination, press [img src=ic_reached/] to proceed to the next stage.\nNow you can play a minigame! After finishing it, the checkpoint will be marked as complete.\nComplete more checkpoints to earn experience and level up!</string>
    <string name="games">Sudoku : Each row, column and square needs to be filled out with the numbers 1–9, without repeating any numbers within the row, column or square. Select an empty cell then choose one of the 9 numbers below or X to clear the cell.\nColorLink : You have to create a line between each two cells with the same colour. To do that, click on one of the two cells, then click each empty cell that will be part of the line until you reach the other cell of the same colour. You can go from a cell only to neighbouring cells horizontally or vertically. Clicking a cell from the created line will delete the path starting from that point.\nFindWord : You will need to find a number of romanian words in a period of time. The words will be given one after another and to mark one as found you will need to click on the first and the last of its letters in the table. If the time runs out you will have to retry the game with other words.</string>
    <string name="creditsText">Mind Your Way was created by:\n\nGiugioiu Marian\nPasoi Stefan\nRotaru Iulian\nSimion Cristian</string>
</resources>

